FALLEN HEROES
This is lame!
Hey! How about a little respect?
Elely, Iops may be dumb and impulsive,
but one thing's for sure,
they don't give up easily.
How did you do that? You're so strong!
A lot less than I used to be.
A whole lot less.
Do you miss your arm?
It was my favorite arm,
my best punching arm in fact.
Of course I miss it, but it's not so bad.
I could have lost a lot more.
Don't you miss your adventures with Mama?
You guys are our adventure now, sweetie.
Okay, I miss it a little sometimes.
Your mother and I met
in the middle of a battle.
It doesn't get more romantic than that!
And adventure after adventure,
the villains we took on
only got more powerful.
Nox, the mad Xelor...
Rushu, the mad demon,
and Qilby, the mad Eliatrope.
-Ogrest...
-The mad ogre?
Yeah, how'd you guess?
That was the biggest one.
Yugo helped take him down.
You caught that dragon by the horns.
It's crazy how you and Yugo managed
to win the fight! It was so cool!
It was great. And an arm isn't
a high price for a fight like that!
You gave that Ogrest the beating
of his life and with that dragon you...
Dally!
You're still outside?
Speaking of dragons...
I heard that, Iop brain.
You need to stop all this training.
It's freezing.
-You'll catch cold dressed that way.
-Get used to it!
Soon I'll have another little Iop
to teach the ropes to.
Please don't.
Ah, they're so gross.
And I've seen them do much worse.
Rubi!
Not my fault if you forget to take me off
the wall when you do private exercises.
Enough, Rubi, we get the idea.
You dirty old Shushu.
I can't believe this!
Such a bad temper.
She inherited it from her mother.
It's going to be very cold tonight.
Let's eat before the soup is
as cold as we are.
Again with the soup?
Set the table, kids.
-It's Flopin's turn!
-In your dreams, Iop head!
Flopin, put out the spoons.
Elely, get the bowls. Quick!
It's not fair!
-I love your soup, Mama.
-Big suck-up!
No, if I was a suck-up,
I'd tell Mama about
your mega training session tomorrow,
a trek through snow,
swimming in an icy river...
-A whole load of stupid Iop stuff.
-What?
Traitor!
Look outside, Dally! No way
are you two going out tomorrow.
We can't just sit by the fireside all day.
In this weather,
that's what normal people do!
Someone's at the door.
It's probably just the beams creaking.
We're alone out here.
Okay, not the beams.
Hello, good sir.
The storm took me by surprise and...
I don't have the right gear with me.
There's a bear at the door who says
he's cold. But you have fur.
Hello, everyone. I'm a Pandawa.
Stop being so rude and let him in.
The poor thing must be frozen solid.
Thank you!
I have to ask you
to leave your weapons at the door.
All of them?
Why? How many have you got?
Oh, a few.
I feel like I've lost 200 pounds.
All right, I think that's it.
Not all of it.
What do you mean, not all of it?
I already feel naked.
Steady, I was talking about your balls.
You must mean these.
These are my marbles.
The kids and I can play a match later on.
Cool!
In any case, noble family,
thank you for your hospitality.
You haven't tried Mama's soup yet.
My name is Poo, Pandawa adventurer.
Hello, Poo. We're the Sadlygrove family.
These are our children, Elely and Flopin,
my husband, Percedal, and I'm Evangelyne.
You... You're Percedal and Evangelyne
from the Brotherhood of the Tofu?
Well, even in the middle of nowhere,
people know our names.
I can't believe I've run into you.
What luck!
You're not just famous, you're legends.
You, Princess Amalia, the great
Ruel Stroud, Yugo the Eliatrope...
You all became legends.
Amalia?
Amalia!
Aren't you enjoying your meal?
Of course, it's delicious.
But your mind is elsewhere, little sister.
We'll take your mind off
whatever's bothering you.
Don't worry about me, Aurora.
I wanted to introduce you to someone
you have a lot in common with.
Mighty Sadidas, good day.
You may rise, Ashdur! Now give us
a little overview of your talents.
Right! A show of strength!
Oh, bravo! How magnificent!
Yeah, it's good. And who is that?
I thought you'd introduced me
to all your brothers.
Amalia, show the lady some respect!
It's all right, my prince,
Amalia didn't mean any harm.
She's right,
but when will you realize I'm not a child
and I know what you are trying to do?
You're her cousin, right?
Yeah, I knew it!
Even family dinners
are all about politics.
-But--
-From now on, I'll eat in my room.
What a little brat!
Don't worry, my prince. We'll weed
the disobedience out of her in the end.
Father... You have to get better soon.
Without you, the Sadida Kingdom
is a shadow of what it was.
You've had another fight
with your brother, haven't you?
His wife is just as pushy as he is.
They're trying so hard.
I can't do this without you.
Do you know how much
you look like your mother?
Soon, I will join her and the prospect...
fills me with joy.
And you, my little bud, you will blossom.
You just need to find out which way
to turn to receive the love you need.
I already know what I need, Father.
It's the third time
we've come looking for Adamai.
I don't see why your brother
is in these ruins.
I'm sorry about before, but...
You need the Dofus.
I told you I don't agree.
-What's got into you?
-I'm the one who should be sensible?
You're risking the world for Dally!
I won't give you the Dofus.
We've always been there for each other,
Ad, and Dally is like a brother to us.
Do you think he'd want you
to risk the world to save him
and put Eva and the children in danger?
I'll be careful, Ad.
You don't even know how to use them.
-I'm learning fast.
-Really?
Ad, the Dofus are being used
for bad reasons.
They are in the process
of destroying the world.
We can change that with ours!
No!
I will not change my mind, Yugo.
You have to choose
between your friend and your brother.
If I listen to you, Ad...
...there wouldn't be anyone left
to choose between.
I love you, brother.
I don't understand.
We were looking for him for months.
He can't just have disappeared.
That sure was good!
Yup, he's definitely a Pandawa.
I want to give you something
for your kind hospitality.
Children, I'm going to lend you my balls.
Awesome!
The idea is simple.
You have to wait until they light up,
then you'll get an unforgettable show.
As for you, my kind hosts,
I want to show you an unforgettable trick.
All right! I love tricks!
Here we go! It's starting!
Dally! No!
Mama!
You didn't come here
out of pure chance, you hairball.
There's no room for chance
in this world.
Tell me what you want. It'll be quicker.
Your children and Eva,
since she's pregnant.
Save your breath, Poo.
Get him out of the way.
He won't let us leave without a struggle.
There's no hurry, Toxine.
Take Eva outside. Silo, you follow her.
My blade is poisoned, Sir Percedal.
If it touches her neck,
you'll never see her again.
The children, take care of the children.
You took me by surprise,
but it won't happen again.
-Dirty...
-I'm not the only one.
-She learned that from me.
-Behind you, Papa!
He's good.
Hide in the forest, kids!
I'll get your mother.
In your dreams!
We're going back to crush 'em!
Flopin, you go hide, okay?
You're pregnant, Evangelyne.
Don't put your baby in harm's way.
Thanks for the advice!
Hurry up and get them before they escape.
Before we escape?
Why would we try to escape?
Maybe they think we're afraid, Eva,
but I'm sure we just kicked their butts.
A major spanking!
Can I go get them, Papa? Please say I can!
I'm not sure, you can never tell,
maybe they are dangerous.
Stop acting like we don't exist!
You're doing pretty well,
but you're making a grave error
by underestimating us.
Shut up, Poo! You three are ridiculous!
No, wait, let us finish!
You promised you'd let...
Shut up and watch!
That voice...
Adamai?
Eva, take the kids
and get as far away as you can.
-But...
-Fast!
You're not going to like this,
but we need to take your children.
We have very big plans for them.
Yeah? Well, I've got a big plan, too.
Making sure you never attack
my family again!
Show-off!
His... His back...
Those are... the Eliatrope Dofus.
Not bad, huh? They give my powers a boost.
But... Goultard was guarding them.
Yes, it wasn't easy taking them from him.
He's an Iop god,
you can't have beaten him.
I cheated a little.
Adamai, I don't know what happened,
but we can figure this out.
Mama!
I've always dreamed of doing that.
Honestly, Dally,
I don't know how you can stand her.
Are you even trying now, my friend?
It's almost... annoying.
Papa!
What happened to you?
We used to be like brothers!
I have new brothers now.
A family who opened up my eyes.
I know what I have to do
with people like you. It's crystal-clear.
People like me?
All of you must be stopped... now!
I don't know what you're talking about.
All I know is Yugo will never forgive you.
Yugo? Do you want to say hi to him?
Dally...
Let me go!
As you wish!
Dally!
I won't leave you alone, Papa.
My darling little Iop...
Ad... Sorry, the little girl got away.
Even guarding a little girl
is too much to ask?
Well, you and your superpowers
couldn't stop her either.
I suppose you're right, Poo,
I'm sorry I got carried away.
Go find them... and meet me at the tower.
Papa!